Alice Shulevska

Architect

Email: shulevskaya.alise@gmail.com

Address: Glen Rock, NJ **Phone:** +1 (551) 276-9227

Nationality: Ukrainian (Eligible to work in the US)



Objective

I am a creative and enthusiastic architect from Kharkiv, Ukraine fueled by a passion for design, collaboration, and purpose-driven architecture. With 2.5 years of professional experience in leading Ukrainian architecture companies, I am now looking for new opportunities to apply my talent and creativity, learn, and collaborate with like-minded people.

Education

National Kharkiv University of Civil Engineering and Architecture Bachelor of Architecture and City Planning

Sep 2019 – Jun 2021

Kharkiv College of Construction, Architecture, and Design Architecture and Interior design – Associate Degree Sep 2014 – Jun 2019

Experience

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022

Project meneger assistent - Ukrsantechproekt,

Kharkiv, Ukraine

- Develop detailed design concepts and construction documentation
- Participated in design ideation workshops
- Participated in client meetings
- Assisted in project management, led work of other team members, organized workflow
- Mentored younger staff
- Assisted in construction administration
- Produced rapid visualization of concepts
- Provided expertise in executing projects to team members, clients, and contractors

Sep 2019 - Jan 2021

Jr. Architect, Kharkovproject, Kharkiv, Ukraine

- Assisted in model building
- Worked on construction documents and redlines
- Participated in specification writing
- Assisted in preparation for design competitions
- Built company website

Skills

- Revit
- ArchiCAD
- AutoCAD
- Lumion
- Sketch Up
- Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Word
- Excel

- Strong conceptual design and schematic design skills
 - Strong verbal and graphic communication skills
- Ability to work within diverse teams of designers
- Ability to participate in multiple projects and manage deadlines
- Language skills
- Strong organizational skills
- Critical thinking

Languages

- English (Completed upper-intermediate English-language course at Atlas Language School, Dublin, Ireland)
 - Ukrainian
- Russian

Projects

Soccer Stadium - Mariupol city, Ukraine - Competition project for Soccer World Cup (UEFA Europa League Group Stage, 12.500-seat stadium

Kramatorsk Medical University - Kramatorsk, Ukraine

Concept project for reconstruction of administrative buildings. The project was developed within the Program "Our Kramatorsk" was initiated by the European Investment Bank for Reconstruction of Ukraine

Kharkiv Art Museum - Kharkiv, Ukraine - Developed a concept project for the program of the President of Ukraine "Great Restoration"

Hobbies

- Painting
- Hiking